eximdesk.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated on 5th Jan 2015

### General:

This Privacy Policy Statement applies to all of the products and services offered by Eximdesk.com or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies ("The Company", "FrontalRain Technologies Pvt. Ltd", "Eximdesk","we", "us", "our", and terms of similar meaning) and is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have such meaning as ascribed to the term in the Terms. The User shall hereinafter be collectively referred to as the "you", "your", "the User" and any other terms that bear similar meaning

This Privacy Policy covers and describes how we collect, use and disclose information that we collect through the website: [www.eximdesk.com](http://www.eximdesk.com/), our subdomains and our service (Eximdesk).

### Information Recorded and Use:

### Personal Information 

When you sign up for the Services or promotions that require registration, we seek the personal information of the User (such as name, company name, email address, phone number and other personal information as well as your business information). For our Users we also maintain User Data which is managed differently as explained in a later section. Eximdesk collects information under the direction of its Users, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes within the platform. 

By using the site you consent to the collection, storage and use of your browsing sequence on this website. We share this information with trusted 3rd parties only for the purpose of showing you marketing communications of interest. No personally identifiable information is shared except when the law requires so or it is permitted in terms of this policy. We do not otherwise sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally identifying information of our users. 

### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information:

To review and update, correct or delete your personal information and to ensure it is accurate, you may login into your account to make the changes, or you may contact us at [support@eximdesk.com](mailto:support@eximdesk.com).

### Access to Data Controlled by our Users:

FrontalRain Technologies has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes through the Eximdesk system. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the FrontalRain Technologies's User (the data controller). If the User requests FrontalRain Technologies to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

### Log Information:

Upon access of the Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Eximdesk stores temporarily or as an intermediary User information on computers that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. The Company records the IP address(es) of each user of the Site and tracks it's Users by the use of "Clickstream Cookies" inter-alia in compliance with statutory regulations and for security reasons.

### Usage Details:

Your usage details including without limitation the time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used and the amount of storage used will be recorded by us for among other reasons, security concerns.

### User communications:

When you send an email or other communications to FrontalRain Technologies, we retain those communications.

### User Data:

FrontalRain Technologies will not review, share, distribute, or reference any User Data except as provided herein or the Terms,or as may be required by law. Individual records of User Data may be viewed or accessed for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the Terms of Service, or as may be required by law. Users are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their user ids and passwords.

### Contents of your User Account:

We store and maintain files, documents, to-do lists, emails and other data stored in your user account at centralized Eximdesk designated facilities. In order to prevent loss of data due to errors or system failures, we also keep backup copies of data including the contents of your user account. Hence your files and data may remain on our servers even after deletion or termination of your user account. We assure you that the contents of your user account will not be disclosed to anyone and will not be accessible even to employees of Eximdesk except in circumstances specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy Statement and Terms of Service. We also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Data Retention:

FrontalRain Technologies will retain personal data we process through the platform on behalf of our Users for as long as needed to provide services to our User. FrontalRain Technologies will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Data integrity:

FrontalRain Technologies collects, processes and reviews all User Data only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service or under law.

FrontalRain Technologies processes the various information you provide to offer solutions and results to you, as may be required for providing and enhancing the Services including without limitation:

    * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
    * Aggregating usage patterns, trends and other statistics;
    * Developing new services;
    * FrontalRain Technologies may also use data about Users for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in FrontalRain Technologies, the Service, and to send you information regarding the Company and its partners, such as information about promotions or events; and
    * On occasion we use email address or other contact information to contact our Users to ask them for their input on our services. We may also use your email address to send you promotional emails and update you about our latest products. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [info@eximdesk.com](mailto:info@eximdesk.com). We may also use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze our website usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize our website's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our website and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using our website.

### Information sharing:

All the information requested by the user for publishing by the user will be checked and published by the Eximdesk to the intended audience. User Profile, Product Catalog, Website, Emails, Chats messages, comments, documents which are meant for sharing will be shared with the intended parties and users are request to take sufficient precautions before initiating these actions in the software. 

Further if you submit any information to be published on the site including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog, Product Pictures, Trade Leads then you are deemed to have given your consent to the publication of such information.

FrontalRain Technologies shares User Data and any other information with other companies or individuals outside of FrontalRain Technologies in the following limited circumstances:

    * We provide such information to our agents who have been engaged to perform functions on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These parties are authorized to use such information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
    * To (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of FrontalRain Technologies, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
    * If FrontalRain Technologies becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of its assets. In this case, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

However, we would like to state that no system can guarantee absolute security although, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. All information collected from the User or that falls within the possession of Eximdesk is held on secure servers hosted by Eximdesk. However, the nature of internet is such that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. However, we have assured to take such reasonable steps as laid out in these terms to protect your data.

We employ various security measures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure proper use of information. These measures are both electronic as well as physical but at the same time no data transmission over the net can be guaranteed to be 100 % secure. Also it is advised to please keep in mind that the personal and business information posted online is accessible to the public and hence you may receive unsolicited communication from other parties. 

In order to support many of the services that we provide on a free basis to our visitors we display advertisements based on usage trends and visitor statistics. User's personal and business information is used to serve targeted advertising through the companies websites, customized e-mailers, newsletters etc. Further once the users information is displayed on the websites the user may start receiving enquiries through SMS, Mails, Phone etc over which Eximdesk has no control. 

### Cookies:

We use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance your experience of our Services. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. Permanent cookies or persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory [(Information on cookies).](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie "Clicke here for more information on cookies") If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the website. We tie cookie information to your user id when you elect to remain logged in so as to maintain and recall your preferences within the website.

We may from time to time employ the services of a third party agent to analyze statistical and aggregate data about our website content and user base. This aggregated information is not personally identifiable and is employed in improving website functionality and offerings. To this end, these third parties may employ the use of cookies and, or pixel tags in providing their services. While these third party cookies are not tied to your User Data, Eximdesk does not have access to these cookies nor are we responsible for them.

### Social Media Widgets:

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Links from our website:

Some pages of our website contain external links over which we have no control. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal information, without assuring yourselves of the Privacy Policy Statement of other websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback from you with regard to those linked sites.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties through such external links, whether they are subscribers or Users or otherwise, different rules may apply to their use, collection and disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. Since we do not control the information use, collection or disclosure policies of third parties, you are subject to their privacy policies. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### How secure is your Information:

We adopt industry appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your user account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees and agents who need to know such information in connection with providing Services to you and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

Salient security features from the physical and network perspectives are:

    * Physical security provided at the data center like biometric access, surveillance cameras, photo id card, etc.
    * Network level security consisting of Robust Firewalls and Intrusion Detection Systems;
    * Dedicated Personnel at the centralized Eximdesk designated facilities will monitor both the above on a 24X7 basis

Salient Security Features from an Application perspective are:

    * Service provided on https protocol ensuring encryption of data and secure transmission.
    * Comprehensive Application level security addressing issues like access level checking, SQL Injection, etc.
    * Facility to configure a password policy, to enforce stronger and more secure passwords
    * Backups of application and database on a regular basis

FrontalRain Technologies uses robust security measures to protect User Data from unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure the appropriate use of User Data. When the Service is accessed using Internet Explorer version 9.0 or later, Firefox version 14.0 or later, or Safari version 3.0 or later, or Google Chrome 21.0 or later, Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology protects User Data using both server authentication and data encryption. These technologies help ensure that User Data is safe, secure, and only available to the User to whom the information belongs and those to whom the User has granted access. FrontalRain Technologies also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and the Company hosts its Web sites in a secure server environment that uses firewalls and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. Because the Company uses the Service to maintain Data about FrontalRain Technologies' Users, this information is secured in the same manner as described above for User Data.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information:

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy and in Terms of Service. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide our services:

Third party licensing agreement: User would be required to enter into a third party licensing agreement for the provision of Services in the manner as set out in Terms of Service.

Legal Requests: In the event of Emergencies, FrontalRain Technologies may disclose your personal information (a) to any governmental authority as part of an investigation to determine our compliance with any applicable law, rule, or regulation (including privacy laws, rules, and regulations), (b) in response to a court order, subpoena, discovery request, or other lawful judicial or administrative proceeding, (c) as otherwise required under any applicable law, rule, or regulation, and (d) in good faith, to protect or defend the rights or property of Eximdesk and other users.

We may post your company logo and testimonial along with your name on our website. If you want your logo or testimonial to be removed please contact us at [support@eximdesk.com](mailto:support@eximdesk.com).

### Choice:

We collect information for our Users through the platform, if you are an employee of one of our Users and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Users that use our service, please contact the User that you interact with directly.

EXIMDESK respects your right to Opt Out. We may use Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on the site. Google's use of the DART cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our Users based on their visits to our Websites and /or other sites on the net. Also analytics and on site personalization services are provided by Adobe as well as advertising services to help companies measure the use of their websites or tailor their online ads based on the likely interests of their users. 

### Investigation of Illegal Activity:

We may need to provide access to your personal information and the contents of your user account to our employees and service providers for the purpose of investigating any suspected illegal activity or potential violation of the terms and conditions for use of Eximdesk Services. However, Eximdesk will ensure that such access is in compliance with this Privacy Policy Statement and subject to appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

### Enforcement of Privacy Policy:

We make every effort, including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this Privacy Policy Statement. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this Privacy Policy Statement or the manner in which Personal Information is used for the purpose of providing Eximdesk Services, kindly contact Eximdesk User Support Services at [support@eximdesk.com](mailto:support@eximdesk.com) or write to us at:

### Privacy Matters:

C/O FrontalRain Technologies Pvt. Ltd.  
2nd Floor, Sona Towers,  
71/2, Millers Road, Bangalore - 560052  
Phone: +91-80-41203849 - Email: [info@eximdesk.com](mailto:info@eximdesk.com)

We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard if needed.

### Notification of Changes:

Any changes to the Privacy Policy Statement will be posted on our website in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected, manner of collection, use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use your information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email prior to the change becoming effective and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses unless you have opted out from receiving all email notifications from us. You will not receive email notification of minor changes to the Privacy Policy Statement.

### End of Privacy Policy:

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at [info@eximdesk.com](mailto:info@eximdesk.com). We shall respond to all inquiries within 30 days of receipt upon ascertaining your identity.
